municode.com 2005-12-31

# Municode.com | Privacy Policy

* * *

## This privacy notice contains the following sections:

  * Introduction
  * Information Collection
  * Information Usage
  * Problem Resolution
  * Data Storage and Security
  * Contact information

### Introduction

Municipal Code Corporation respects each individuals right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at Municipal Code Corporations Web site.

While the majority of access to information provided on the Municode Web site is offered free of charge, we do charge fees for select premium products and services. The initial product for which a fee is charged is Multiple Code Searching, which enables subscribers to query more than one Code simultaneously. To enable the purchase of these products Municipal Code Corporation collects billing and credit card information. The credit card information is not archived. This information will only be shared with third parties who perform tasks required to complete the purchase transaction. 

### Part I. Information Collection

Municipal Code Corporation collects information through our Web site at several points. We collect the following information about primary visitors: 

  * The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and Internet Protocol (IP) address from which you access our site; 
  * The type of hardware, browser and operating system used to access our site; 
  * The date and time you access our site; 
  * The number of bytes of data transmitted during your visit; 
  * Transaction and routing information to and from your computer; 
  * The pages you visit; and 
  * If you linked to our site from another Web site, the address of that Web site (URL). 

We collect additional information through order forms and support forms. The information collected through these forms is solely that which the user provides and is voluntarily given.

Municipal Code Corporation makes use of cookies on its web site. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a users computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. They are used to enable special functions such as setting the "Online Codes" page as the users home page on municode.com should the user request it, or remembering that you are a registered user of a premium service. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and with exception of the "Online Codes Home Page" and registered user cookies, they expire when you leave the site. 

### Part II. Information Usage.

We consider any information that could reasonably be used to identify you as "personally identifying information." This may include: 

  * Your name;
  * Your address (excluding zip code);
  * Your E-mail address;
  * Your social security number;
  * Your password;
  * Bank account information;
  * Credit card information;
  * License or identification number;
  * Telephone number;
  * Medical or disability information;
  * Any combination of data that could be used to identify you such as birth date, zip code and gender; and
  * Any graphical or visual representation of you.

If personal information is requested on the Web site or volunteered by the user, State law and the federal Privacy Act of 1974 may protect it. However, this information is no longer protected once you provide it, and may be subject disclosure. Any personally identifying information you provide will be stored in a limited access server, and we maintain safeguards to protect the security of the information.

We do not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources, nor do we sell or share information collected from our Web site with others. We may, however, use information collected to process, validate and verify subscriptions; or to enhance existing features or develop new features; or to send you e-mails about new services or features; or to personalize the content you and others see.

We offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours.

Our Web site offers a List-Serv mailing list. Please be advised that information posted in these venues is accessible by members of the lists. 

If our policy on information collection or uses changes, this page will be updated to reflect these changes.

### Part III. Problem Resolution

If problems arise, users may contact Municipal Code Corporation at the email addresses listed here. We are committed to resolving disputes as soon as possible.

### Part IV. Data Storage and Security

Municipal Code Corporation protects user information with the following security measures:

  * Secure servers verified by [Verisign](https://digitalid.verisign.com/as2/4c49d413f2e47d8e72066d151ae827ba)
  * SSL encryption
  * Database Encryption
  * Firewalls
  * Disaster preparedness procedures
  * Employee screening

If you have any further questions about privacy or security, please contact us by sending an email to: .

This policy was last updated on February 15, 2005.
  *[SSL]: Secure Socket Layer technology
